THAMMACHART NIMKHIAO

PROGRAMMER, IT STAFF

Samutprakarn, Thailand | +66 80 429 9141 | thammachart.n@gmail.com



Summary

Currently I'm PHP Developer. I'm graduate with a Bachelor of Science degree. (Computer Science), Faculty of Science, Maejo University. Have some experience working on programming and IT support. I personally like working with database, for example, MySQL, PostgreSQL, etc.

Education

Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science Maejo University, Chiang Mai, Thailand

A beginner PHP developer

High School Certificate

StreeSamutprakarn School, Samutprakarn, Thailand

Secondary School

Work experience

PHP PROGRAMMER

November 2017 - Present

2012 - 2016

2006 - 2011

Yuasa Battery (Thailand) Public Co., Ltd., Samutprakarn, Thailand

Responsibilities

- Design and analysis system.
- Create web application to help employees to work with PHP Programming (Laravel Framework).
- Developing and creating C# with Microsoft SQL Server database and PHP with MySQL database applications as per the specifications.
- Performing the responsibilities of implementing and hosting of systems on a web server
- Testing and analyzing programming projects and reporting the same to the programming manager.

PHP PROGRAMMER

November 2016 - October 2017

IS CODE Co., Ltd., Bangkok, Thailand

Responsibilities

- keeping track of website visits, updating new content displays on websites
- Developing and creating C# with Microsoft Server database and PHP with MySQLdatabase applications as per the specifications
- Performing the responsibilities of implementing and hosting of systems on a web server
- Coordinating with team members in developing database structure
- Testing and analyzing programming projects and reporting the same to the programming manager

Personal Information

- Date of Birth: 10 October1993
- Place of Birth: Samutprakarn, Thailand
- Nationality: Thai
- Marital Status: Single

Programming Skills

HTML + CSS

I like to decorate the website by using

HTML and CSS.

PHP

I know the basics of the language.

TKHOW the basics of the language.

My graduation project was a PHP website.

C#

I know the basics of the language.

Javascript

I know the basics of the language.

JAVA

I know the basics of the language.

Languages Skills

- English: Intermediate
- Thai: Mother Tongue

Portfolio

ISUZU Motors Co., (Thailand) Ltd., Samutprakarn, Thailand

Responsibilities

- Installed and performed maintenance on domain controller, active directory, printer network, AS400 program, database server (SQL), mail server by Microsoft Exchange Server
- Developed programs for manage department by JAVA, PHP, RPG/AS400
- Designed Basic LAN network.
- Service Desktop PCs and Laptop.
- Responsible for determining software and hardware resolutions.
- Work as primary support analyst for company.
- Responsible for training the new staff on PC and Network basics.
- Performed server updated on regular basis.
- Always stayed up-to-date about software.

- Web application for French food restaurant in Japan.
- Web application for Comcamp 14th Maejo University.

Experience

Short-term Student Exchange

August 2015 - December 2015

Keio University Shonan Fujisawa Campus, Fujisawa, Japan

- Join the database structure class in Multimedia Database Laboratory.
 - Studied 5D World Map.
 - Studied finding distance in the databaseby Spatial-Relationship Computation.
 - Studied finding time periods in database by Temporal-Relationship Computation.
- Help lab works.
 - Assisted in the preparation of a presentation on the occasion of the Keio University Shonandai Fujiwara Campus 25th Anniversary.
- Develop web application.
 - Product Alerts using Trigger in PostgreSQL database.
 - Store food database of French restaurants "Tokyo Kaikan" web application.

Trainee May 2015 - July 2015

ISUZU Motors Co., (Thailand) Ltd., Samutprakarn, Thailand

- Developed Data Damaged computer equipment Java programing.
- Repaired basic problem computer and software.
- Repaired and upgraded old systems, installed then configure new systems.

Hobbies

- Traveling
- Reading article about technology
- Watching Movies
- Listening to music
- Jogging

References

Miss. Chalitda Madhyamapurush

Professor Maejo University.

Email: mchalitda@gmail.com